Hello Hello Friends in this video we are going to talk
about ICICI Lombard's Q3 2022 results and we are talking about Ravindra
Operations, that was the last 158 ​​floor
profit was seen to be less than 6% but the
track number flight applicant
profit for Tiger Shroff is 121 crore
festival official turn was seen to be going down by 20%, the
operating profit of that is very strong,
hey your recent turn in this quarter
it is seen to be going down by 40 percent of the time, so
revenue profit operating
profit three, we have not shown such a good turn here, the
turn quarter it
is definitely in revenue but the profit and operating
profit is added here, that is shown if we
look at the operating margin, then there is
7 percent, friend Rihand basis points do and cotton 2482 joins from this point, set, talking about 318 crore black color, it
definitely showed a strong increase of 2 percent but the turn was seen to be going down by 20%,
decision of 7.47  Last 13 was
at number six and here last
quarter was at number nine, Toral see how
good it looks and
show the acting by putting tomato in the lecturer but
we will see the profit graphic and profitability, so
in both the three we are
just seen falling here and I have
opened my second channel where
I have uploaded a new video and the clean bank
link is in the description, the link of rice is also
in the description, if you are
interested in this topic then you can check the nap video
or please go to the channels and
subscribe to it, as there also we are going to
bring very good interesting videos,
we will meet in the next video, till then
why do you need